

DENIZ ARDA MURAT

Software Developer

• İzmit, TR

+90 507 378 58 54

☑ denizardamrt@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/denizardamrt

Skills

Flutter

JavaScript

. . _ _

MSSQL

Angular

NodeJS

Summary

I graduated from Marmara University Electrical-Electronics Engineering at 2022. Since my last year at university I have worked as a Software Developer. While working I worked with a lot of different technologies for web development. I developed mobile applications with flutter and upload them to App and Play stores. For database, I have a good knowledge on MSSQL. With these technologies I developed various applications on IT sector.

Work experience

2021-10

Software Developer

PremierTurk Bilgi Teknolojileri A.Ş, Kocaeli, TR

Flutter,.NET,MSSQL,NodeJS,Angular,AngularJs,

2021-07 -

Software Developer Intern

2021-08

PremierTurk Bilgi Teknolojileri A.Ş, Kocaeli, TR

HTML,CSS,Javascript,AngularJS,C#,Windows Forms,MSSQL,Web API

Education

12.09.2016 -

Electrical and Electronics Engineering

15.08.2022

Marmara University

Languages

Turkish

English

Upgrace to Pro to remove this watermark